Finding Aid for School of Natural Resources and Environment (University of Michigan) Publications 1903-2011
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- Sub-Unit Publications
  - Minority Environmental Leadership Development Initiative
    - Brochures undated (Box 7)
    - Programs
      - National Summit on Diversity in the Environmental Field 2005 (Box 7)
    - Reports
      - Summary Results of the MELDI Studies 2005 (Box 7)
  - National Pollution Prevention Center
    - Directory and Educational Materials 1997 (Box 7)
  - Natural Resource Sociology Research Lab
    - Reports
      - Indian SIA: The Social Impact Assessment of Rapid Resource Development on Native Peoples, 1982 (Box 7)
      - Michigan Sport Angler's Fish Consumption Survey, 1989 (Box 7)
      - Natural Resource Bureaucracy and Rural Poverty: A Study in the Political Sociology of Natural Resources, 1982 (Box 7)
  - Office of Academic Programs
    - Brochures
      - School of Natural Resources and Environment, 1992 (Box 7)
  - Program in the Environment
    - Brochures undated (Box 7)
    - Newsletters
      - Crossroads, 2006 (Box 8)
  - Project for the Study of Natural Resources and Environmental Conflict
    - Reports undated (Box 8)
  - Research Development Program
    - Reports
      - Research Development Program: Histories, Status, Direction, 1984 (Box 8)
  - Student Policy Advisory Committee
    - Newsletters
      - Great ExSpactations, 1986-1987 (Box 8)
      - SPAC Connections, 1982-1985 (Box 8)
  - Urban and Regional Planning Ph.D. Program
    - Newsletters
      - URP Post, 1981-1982 (Box 8)
  - Wildland Management Center
    - Brochures undated (Box 8)
    - Newsletters
      - Endangered Species, 1983-1988 v. 1-6 (Box 8)
      - WMC News/Notes, 1984 (Box 8)
    - Reports
      - Eastern Caribbean Natural Area Management Program: Annual Report, 1985 (Box 8)
      - A Regional Conservation Strategy for the Great Lakes Basin: A Preliminary Assessment, 1984 (Box 8)
- Topical Publications
  Topical Publications include materials relating to Alumni of the School of Natural Resources.
  - 100th anniversary 2003 (Box 8)
  - Alumni
    - Directories
      - Alumni Directory
        - 1904-1924 (Box 8)
        - 1914-1985 (Box 8)
        - Landscape Architecture 1982 (Box 8)
      - Directory of Alumni and Former Students 1949-1951 (Box 8)
      - Directory of Alumni by Regions 1904-1928 (Box 8)
      - Directory of Alumni, Former Students and Faculty 1961 (Box 8)
    - Programs
      - Alumni Banquet (Box 8)
- Student Publications
  Student Publications are printed materials produced by students of the School of Natural Resources. These include newsletters such as Au Naturel, Natural Resources Review, The Resource, SNR Reporter, Synergy and Timber Cruiser.
  - Newsletters
    - Au Naturel, 1971 (Box 8)
    - Natural Resources Review, no. 1-2, 1972 (Box 8)
    - The Resource: A Newsletter for People in the School of Natural Resources, v. 1, 1978 (Box 8)
    - SNR Reporter, 1972-1975 (Box 8)
    - Synergy: Literary Journal of the School of Natural Resources, 1983-1984 (Box 8)
    - Timber Cruiser, 1965 (Box 8)
- Archived SNRE Website
  The Website series documents the academic programs, accomplishments, resources, events, and people at the School of Natural Resources and Environment. Content includes important news and announcements, publications (such as newsletters and course catalogs), and information about admissions, curriculum, degree requirements, faculty, and the overall mission of the School. The website series is arranged chronologically and includes content captured by the Internet Archive starting in 1997 as well as captures provided by Bentley Library archivists in 2002, 2004, and 2008. Starting in 2010, this archived website will be captured on a regular, ongoing basis as part of the University of Michigan Web Archives, hosted at http://webarchives.cdlib.org/a/universityofmichigan/.
  - Home Page
    - 1997-[ONGOING]
      (These versions were preserved by the Internet Archive and are made available through its Wayback Machine. The Bentley Historical Library is not involved in the collection or maintenance of this material.)
    - May 15, 2002, .ZIP file
    - April 20, 2004, .ZIP file
    - May 9, 2008, .ZIP file
    - 2010-[ONGOING]
  - Related Materials: degree requirements, curricula, research, centers and institutes, 2010-[ongoing]